[{"answer": "It better be! I am my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "S s.  my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Nonono, you're my frien", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "my friend, my frien", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "He", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my frien", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my frien", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "my frien", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my frien", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my frien", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "O", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Hey, I spent weeks preparing too, my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh s, s s, my kisses taste like tacos", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Is bery nice. He's so hansome", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hello hello, are you still there", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You want to sign Ms. my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Fuck you", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You'd better stop", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend!!! Oh, you bought me rrrrroses", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I can't stop thinking about you either, my friend", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I'm not gonna let you blow this one chance I have", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Don't you dar", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I make you hot, my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "my friend..", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Mm, yeah.  Oh, my friend.  Oh my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Oh God, my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend..", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Oh, my friend, I adore you", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "EHAGH!  Moooooommmm", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "my friend is naked in my bed", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What? O", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What news", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I can't handle it anymore. All the fame and the my friend spooge, I... I just can't go on living with Ms. my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Stop doing what", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You try being in an oven mitt for two hours", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I can see your lips moving too, culo", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I can see your lips moving", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "See?! I just saw your lips move", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Ow. Look out, muffinhead", "docId": "South-Park-Fat-Butt-And-Pancake-Head.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Get a what with who", "qsentId": 40}]